Student Directory UP152
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Student Directory
1896 -- 2000
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
UP152
1.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the the Student Directory. It provided contact information for students in the Faculty of Arts and Sciences. Until 1943, the listing, called the Register of Students, was bound in with each years' catalog, with the exception of the register for 1918-19, when there was no catalog and the register was bound separately and is included here. The 1952 Directory of Students contained home addresses of students at each of the schools including the Graduate School and the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy. The later editions include telephone numbers.
- Student Directory, 1896 -- 2000; UP152.001; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Student Directory. It provided contact information for students in the Faculty of Arts and Sciences. Until 1943 the listing, called the Register of Students, was bound in with each years' catalog, with the exception of the register for 1918-19, when there was no catalog and the register was bound separately and is included here. The 1952 Directory of Students contained home addresses of students at each of the schools including the Graduate School and the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy. The later editions include telephone numbers.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Student Directory, 1950; UP152.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1952; UP152.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1953; UP152.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1954; UP152.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1955; UP152.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1956; UP152.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1957; UP152.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1958; UP152.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1960-04-01; UP152.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1960-10-01; UP152.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1961; UP152.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1962; UP152.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1963; UP152.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    Additional annotated copy in folder.
  - Student Directory, 1964; UP152.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1966; UP152.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1967; UP152.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1968; UP152.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    Two additional annotated copies in folder.
  - Student Directory, 1971; UP152.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1972 -- 1973; UP152.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Register of Tufts College, 1896 -- 1897; UP152.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Register of Students, 1898 -- 1899; UP152.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Register of Students, 1969-10-01; UP152.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Student Directory, 1972 -- 1974; UP152.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1974 -- 1975; UP152.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1975 -- 1976; UP152.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1976 -- 1977; UP152.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1977 -- 1978; UP152.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1978 -- 1979; UP152.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1979 -- 1980; UP152.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1980 -- 1981; UP152.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory, 1981 -- 1982; UP152.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Supplement to the directory, 1943; UP152.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Supplement to the directory, 1945-03-01; UP152.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Directories, 1945-07; UP152.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Register of students, 1965; UP152.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Register of students, 1918 -- 1919; UP152.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - The Collegiate Web, Tufts University Shop and Restaurant Guide, phone directory, 1996 -- 1997; UP152.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - The Collegiate Web, Tufts University Shop and Restaurant Guide, phone directory, 1999 -- 2000; UP152.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Register of students, 1934 -- 1935; UP152.001.003.00008 (Box 3)